One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wano's Grand Sumo Tournament
السومو الكبير في بلاد وانو
That's a huge lion-dog!
ذلك الكوماينو ضخم
Whose is it?
من يملكه؟
How do we find this Otama kid?
كيف سنجد تلك الطفلة أوتاما؟
The townsfolk wouldn't tell us even if we asked.
لن يخبرنا سكان البلدة حتى لو سألناهم
They're all under Orochi's influence.
فجميعهم منصاعين لأوروتشي
But some of them look like ordinary people, not fighters.
لكن ثمة أشخاص عاديون لا يبدون كمقاتلين
There have always been regular villagers here.
طالما كان سكان هذه البلدة أشخاص عاديين
Until twenty years ago, this was a vibrant castle town.
قبل عشرين سنة، كانت هذه البلدة مفعمة بالحيوية
But one day, Orochi's subordinates came and seized the houses they desired.
ولكن ذات يوم، أتى أتباع أوروتشي وصادروا المنازل التي تعجبهم
Then, except for essential merchants...
وباستثناء التجار الضروريين لتسيير الحياة
everyone was expelled from town.
طُرد الجميع من البلدة
That's the story behind Bakura Town.
هذه حقيقة بلدة باكورا
A sumo wrestler? How did he...?
مصارع سومو؟ كيف؟
Something's going on further into town.
ثمة أمرٌ يحدث وسط البلدة
Since a sumo wrestler came flying out...
...تحليق مصارع سومو في الهواء يدل على
I suppose it's a sumo match.
وجود نزال سومو
Once again, is there no one who can take down...
...كما هو متوقع، لا أحد بوسعه هزيمة
the yokozuna of the Flower Capital, Urashima?!
يوكوزونا عاصمة الزهور أوراشيما
Urashima
أوراشيما مصارع سومو عظيم في بلاد وانو
Another bunch of weaklings.
مجموعة أخرى من الضعفاء-بي
There're more.
مجددًا
Sumo, huh? Sounds fun!
سومو إذًا؟ لا بدّ أنها ممتعة
Urashima so far has fought and bested nineteen wrestlers.
عدد المصارعين الذين واجهوا أوراشيما بلغوا 19 حتى الآن
But when it comes to the number of bones broken, there have been...
...أما الكسور في العظام فقد بلغت
Ten arm bones...
10 أذرع
fifteen leg bones...
15 ساقًا
fifty-two ribs...
52 ضلعًا
four skulls, and...
4 جماجم
seven backbones!
7 أعمدة فقرية
That's eighty-eight bones in total, and four wrestlers are missing!
المجموع 88 عظمة، و4 مصارعين مفقودين
Overwhelming!
فوز ساحق
His strength is inhuman!
قوته تخطت مستوى البشر
The undefeated monster!
إنه الوحش القاهر
Yokozuna Urashima!
اليوكوزونا أوراشيما
Today, we have a special exhibition match!
لدينا اليوم نزال استعراضي خاص
He who defeats Urashima takes home a staggering 500 gold coins!
السلام يسود الأرض
Take down Urashima!
أطيحوا بأوراشيما
I'll bet on you!
سأراهن على المنافسين
You can do it, guys!
ابذلوا جهدكم يا رجال
We have the perfect plan! We'll win the prize!
لدينا خطة مثالية، سنظفر بالجائزة
Beat those jerks!
أطح بذلك الحقير
Lord Urashima!
أوراشيما-ساما
Ready...
استعداد
Go!
انطلاق
Okiku!
أوكيكو
I knew you would come!
توقعت أنكِ ستأتين
This means you've decided to be my wife, right?!
هل قررتِ الزواج بي؟
Excuse me.
المعذرة
You won't be able to hide behind me.
يستحيل أن تختبئي خلفي
I can't believe it!
لا أصدق ذلك
This woman is engaged to Urashima?!
ثمة امرأة مخطوبة من أوراشيما؟
How lucky! She's loved by a yokozuna!
يا لحظها السعيد، إنها محبوبة اليوكوزونا
This is one hell of a scandal!
هذه أخبار عظيمة
What?! The great Urashima has a wife?!
ماذا؟ زوجة أوراشيما؟
His wife?
زوجته؟
No...
كلا
As you saw earlier, his belief is that I will marry him.
شهدتَ بنفسك سابقًا، هو من يريد الزواج بي
Okiku! I have a match in Bakura Town later!
أوكيكو، لدي مباراة في بلدة باكورا لاحقًا-بي
If you're interested, come and see how strong I am!
سأريك مدى قوتي، لذا تعالي لمشاهدتي إن كنتِ مهتمة
My interests do not align with his.
لا أبادله الشعور نفسه
I see.
فهمت
You guys!
أنتم
We're looking for someone!
نحن نبحث عن أحد
She's a little girl named Tama!
إنها فتاة صغيرة تُدعى تاما
Tell me where this town's boss is!
أخبروني بمكان زعيم هذه البلدة
She should be there!
ستكون عنده حتمًا
That woman is so frustrating! Damn gold digger...!
تلك المرأة، يا للإحباط، ستتزوج رجلًا فاحش الثراء
She's huge, but that's perfect for Urashima!
إنها ضخمة، لكنها امرأة مناسبة لأوراشيما
I'd be a better match!
أنا أنسب منها
They're not listening...
إنهم لا يصغون
Okiku came to see me. Guys, bring her to me!
جاءت أوكيكو لمشاهدتي، أحضروها إلي يا رجال
– Yes, sir!
حاضر
Big Bro! I didn't know you were such a player!
أخي، لم أعلم أنّ ذوقك رفيع في النساء
Everyone wants to be like you! No wonder she fell for you!
لا عجب أنها وقعت في حبك، فأنت قدوتي
Okiku!
أوكيكو
Okay, we're gonna look for her ourselves! Let's go!
سنبحث عنها بأنفسنا، هيا بنا
Hey, lady! Big Bro Urashima wants to see you! Come with us!
أيتها المرأة، أخونا الكبير أوراشيما يطلبكِ، تعالي معنا
Out of our way, jerks!
من أنتم؟ ابتعدوا
Kick their asses!
أطيحوا بهما
Don't get in our way!
لا تعترضوا طريقي
What?!
ماذا؟
Nice charge!
هجوم جيد
I guess the winning technique was a frontal thrust.
أظنني فزت بتقنية الدفع الأمامي
Come with me, lady!
تعالي معي يا امرأة
No... Please stop!
لا، توقف رجاءً
Would you really slash an unarmed naked man?
أستقطع رجلًا عاريًا وأعزل؟
Kiku!
كيكو
Outta my way!
ابتعد
Hey, Zoro! Why did you let them take her away?!
مهلًا زورو، لماذا سمحت لهم؟
I'm sorry...
المعذرة
I thought that it wasn't right...
...قطع رجل عارٍ أعزل
to slash a naked man.
عارٌ عليّ
Besides...
...كما أنها
she's not just a teahouse waitress.
ليست مجرد نادلة في محل شاي
Hey! Isn't she a girl from the teahouse in the other town?!
مهلًا، أليست فتاة محل الشاي من البلدة المجاورة؟
With her rank, it's presumptuous of her to even enter this town!
من الوقاحة لامرأة بمنزلتها أن تدخل هذه البلدة
Is that so?! Then we've gotta kick her out!
فعلًا، يجب طردها
She's a vulgar tramp!
إنها سافلة وضيعة
Shut up, you commoners!
اخرسوا أيها العوام
To us samurai, every one of you fools is the same, vulgar, second-class citizen!
مقارنةً بنا نحن طبقة المحاربين، جميعكم سفلة من الطبقة الدنيا-بي
Your lives are worthless!
حياتكم لا قيمة لها
It's up to me...
فقرار إعفاء أرواحكم أو زهقها
whether you live or die!
نحن من يتخذه
So, Okiku!
لهذا يا أوكيكو
Why don't you...
...لِمَ لا
be...
...تكونين
mine?!
ملكي
This humble servant doesn't know a single citizen...
أنا لا أرى أحدًا ممن تطلق عليهم بالسفلة من الطبقة الدنيا
Enough of your jokes!
كفاك هراءً، لا أحد دنيء هنا سوى قلبك
The yokozuna's topknot!
قنزعة اليوكوزونا
So cool!
رائع
Kiku's got guts!
كيكو تلك بارعة
It's getting exciting now!
ازدادت الأمور إثارة
He got rejected by that woman...
...رفضته امرأة
and got his topknot chopped off!
وقصت قنزعته
That should get their boss out here quickly.
هذه أسرع طريقة لاستدعاء زعيمهم
Okiku!
أوكيكو
You...
...أنتِ
betrayed me!
خنتني
How could I do that...
ليتني لم أفعل ذلك أمام أنظار الجميع
He looks like a wrathful deity!
...إنه يستشيط غضبًا
Okiku!
أوكيكو
Oh no! That pose is...
هذا سيئ، تلك الوضعية
...his Transcendent Slap that sends opponents flying!
إنه هجوم الكف المنبسط الذي يقذف بالخصوم بعيدًا
Please forgive me, Lord Urashima!
أرجوك سامحني يا أوراشيما-ساما
However...
...لكن
It seems that you truly are the kind of man who would hit a woman.
توقعتُ أنك من طينة الرجال الذين يضربون امرأة
Die!
اهلكي
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Sumo Slap!
صفعة السومو زيباري
Damn!
سحقًا
What did you do to my slap?!
كيف صددت هجمة كفي المنبسط؟
Damn you... Who are you to Okiku?!
أيها الوغد، ما علاقتك بأوكيكو؟
Get out of my way!
ابتعد عن طريقي
I have to tear Okiku into bits...
عليّ تمزيق أوكيكو إلى أشلاء
Otherwise I'll lose face!
وإلا فستكون وصمة عار على جبيني
Okay! No problem!
حسنًا، لك ذلك
That is...
...ولكن
Dosukoi!
دوسكوي = تستخدم للتشجيع في مصارعة السومو
If you can beat me!
إن هزمتني فقط
I'm...
...أنا
good at sumo!
بارع في السومو
Luffy-no-umi
لوفي-نو-أومي قرصان ومصارع سومو طموح سجل القتالات: نصر ساحق على أوسوب
Get...
...ابتعد
out of my way!
عن طريقي
Bodhisattva Slap!
الكف البوذية بوساتسو هاريتا
He's dodging Urashima's slaps!
إنه يراوغ هجمات أوراشيما
He's so agile!
يا لرشاقته
Get serious, kiddo!
حظًّا موفقًا أيها القزم
You can't win by just dodging!
لن تنتصر إن اكتفيت بالمراوغة
Ear Smasher!
صمّ الأذن ميمي تسوبش
Hey!
أنت
Eye Gouger!
فقع العين مي تسوبش
Hey! Those are all illegal moves!
مهلًا، أليست هجماتك مخالفة للقوانين؟
Shut up!
اخرس
I'm...
...أنا
a yokozuna!
اليوكوزونا
Well, whatever!
حسنًا، لا يهم
Boss Holdem! We have a problem!
لدينا مشكلة يا هولديم-ساما
Huh? The yokozuna got his topknot chopped off by a woman?
ماذا؟ ثمة امرأة قصّت قنزعة اليوكوزونا؟
Everyone's upset! And we don't know what to do!
الجميع غاضب، ولا نعرف ماذا نفعل
I don't care! What do you expect me to do?!
لا أكترث، ماذا تريدون منّي أن أفعل؟
I'm busy tearing her cheek off!
إنني منشغل بمحاولة أخذ قطعة من خدها
Leave me alone! You can have your baboon back!
ارحمني، يمكنك استعادة البابون
Please stop!
توقف رجاءً
Not a chance!
لن أتوقف
I was told you mentioned the name "Kozuki."
سمعت أنكِ ذكرتِ اسم الكوزكي
When the Kozuki Clan comes back, they'll teach you a lesson!
حينما تعود عشيرة الكوزكي، سيُلقنونكم درسًا لن تنسوه
You must be aware...
ألا تعلمين؟
that saying the name "Kozuki"...
أنّ ذكر اسم عشيرة الكوزكي
is a serious crime!
هي جريمة شنعاء
So this doubles as your punishment.
لذا ما أفعله الآن، يُعد عقوبة على جريمتك أيضًا
You should've stopped chasing ghosts.
لا يجوز التشبّث بالموتى
The Kozuki were an evil clan...
...أرادت عشيرة الكوزكي قبل عشرين سنة
that tried to destroy Wano twenty years ago!
تدمير بلاد وانو
Move it, punk!
ابتعد أيها القزم
There's no fixing what Okiku has done!
ما فعلته أوكيكو مشين للغاية-بي
She turned down the honor of marrying and serving me, a samurai...
رفضت شرف الزواج وخدمة محارب رفيع المستوى مثلي
and tarnished my good name!
لقد لطخت سمعتي
I'll smash her brains in to set an example!
سأسحق رأسها جاعلًا منها كعبرة
Just shut up!
اخرس
Like I said, do as you like once you beat me!
كما أخبرتك، افعل ما تريد بعد هزيمتي
You can't beat me though!
ولكنك لن تستطيع هزيمتي
What do you mean?!
ماذا قلت؟
I'm...
...أنا
the greatest yokozuna in Wano!
أعظم يوكوزونا في بلاد وانو
Transcendent Slap!
ضربة الكف المنبسط هيغان هاريتا
What's this?
ما هذا؟
I don't know. What could it be?
لا أعلم، ما هذا يا ترى؟
You may be a yokozuna...
إذا كنتَ يوكوزونا
but I'm...
...فأنا
the man who's gonna be King of the Pirates!
الرجل الذي سيصير ملك القراصنة
Big Bro Luffy!
أخي الكبير لوفي
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Gigant...
صفعة غيغانت
Sumo Slap!
السومو العملاقة زيباري
Dosukoi
دوسكوي
No...!
...توقف
What the...?
ما هذا؟
A-Am I safe now?
هـ-هل نجوت؟
Th-The yokozuna...
...ا-اليوكوزونا
was sent flying!
قُذف خارج الحلبة
Yokozuna!
اليوكوزونا
No way! He couldn't have lost to a little guy like him!
محال، كيف تمكن هذا القزم من هزيمته؟
That makes me the yokozuna!
أنا اليوكوزونا
I don't care who you are, just bring it on!
هات ما عندك أيًّا تكن
I guess we did enough to get the attention of their boss.
أظننا فعلنا ما يكفي لجذب انتباه زعيمهم
I think so!
أجل
I remember! He's that magistrate killer...!
تذكرته، إنه الرجل الذي قتل القاضي
Zorojuro?!
زوروجورو؟
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Don't tell me he's that guy's ally!
أيعقل أنه رفيق ذلك الرجل؟
Hey!
أنتم
Bring the boss of this town!
استدعوا زعيم هذه البلدة
We're here to take back Tama!
أتينا لاستعادة تاما